<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><idea-plugin>
  <id>com.softwareco.intellij.plugin</id>

  <name>Code Time</name>
  <version>2.2.0</version>

  <vendor email="cody@software.com" url="https://software.com">Software</vendor>

    <description>
      <![CDATA[
      <html>
      <body>
      <p>
      <h1>Code Time</h1>
      </p>

      <p>
      <a href="https://www.software.com/code-time">Code Time</a> is an open source plugin for automatic programming metrics and time-tracking.
      </p>

      <p>
      <img src="https://img.shields.io/jetbrains/plugin/v/10687-code-time.svg"/>
      <img src="https://img.shields.io/jetbrains/plugin/d/10687-code-time"/>
      </p>

      <p>
      <h2>Getting started</h2>
      </p>

      <p>
      <h4>1. Create your web account</h4>
      </p>

      <p>
      <img src="https://swdc-intellij.s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/login-prompt.png"/>
      </p>

      <p>
      The Code Time web app has data visualizations and settings you can customize, such as your work hours and rates per project for advanced time tracking. You can also connect Google Calendar to visualize your Code Time vs. meetings in a single calendar.
      </p>

      <p>
      You can connect multiple code editors on multiple devices using the same email account.
      </p>

      <p>
      <h4>2. Track your progress during the day</h4>
      </p>

      <p>
      <img src="https://swdc-intellij.s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/status-bar.png"/>
      </p>

      <p>
      Your status bar shows you in real-time how many hours and minutes you code each day.
      </p>

      <p>
      <h4>3. Check out your coding activity</h4>
      </p>

      <p>
      To see an overview of your coding activity and project metrics, open the **Code Time panel** by clicking on the Code Time icon in your side bar.
      </p>

      <p>
      <img src="https://swdc-intellij.s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/side-bar.png"/>
      </p>

      <p>
      In your <b>Activity Metrics</b>, your _editor time_ is the total time you have spent in your editor today. Your <i>code time</i> is the total time you have been typing in your editor today. Each metric shows how you compare today to your average and the global average. Each average is calculated by day of week over the last 90 days (e.g. a Friday average is an average of all previous Fridays).
      </p>

      <p>
      You can also see your top files today by KPM (keystrokes per minute), keystrokes, and code time.
      </p>

      <p>
      Your <b>Project Metrics</b> provides a breakdown for the current open project. The _Open changes_ section shows how many lines you have added and deleted before you commit them and the <i>Committed today</i> section summarizes your commits today.
      </p>

      <p>
      <h4>4. Generate your Code Time dashboard</h4>
      </p>

      <p>
      At the end of your first day, open Code Time in your side bar and click <i>Generate dashboard</i> to open your dashboard in a new editor tab. Your dashboard summarizes your coding data—such as your code time by project, lines of code, and keystrokes per minute—today, yesterday, last week, and over the last 90 days.
      </p>

      <p>
      <img src="https://swdc-intellij.s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/editor-dashboard.png"/>
      </p>

      <p>
      <h2>Web app data visualizations</h2>
      </p>

      <p>
      Click "See advanced metrics" in the Code Time side bar or visit <a href="https://app.software.com/">app.software.com</a> to see more data visualizations. Here are a few examples of what you will see in your feed after your first week.
      </p>

      <p>
      <h2>Code Time heatmap</h2>
      </p>

      <p>
      Code Time measures your coding activity per hour and summarizes your data in a weekly and 90-day average heatmap. Protect your best times on your heatmap from meetings and interrupts to help boost your productivity.
      </p>

      <p>
      <img src="https://swdc-vscode.s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/weekly-heatmap.png"/>
      </p>

      <p>
      <h2>Project-based reports</h2>
      </p>

      <p>
      See how much time you spend per project per week. Code Time also lets you set a rate per project and export your data to a CSV.
      </p>

      <p>
      <img src="https://swdc-vscode.s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/top-projects.png"/>
      </p>

      <p>
      <h2>Work-life balance</h2>
      </p>

      <p>
      How much do you code after hours and weekends? Code Time helps you see your breakdown at work vs. outside work so you can find ways to improve your work-life balance.
      </p>

      <p>
      <img src="https://swdc-vscode.s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/work-life-balance.png"/>
      </p>

      <p>
      <h2>Commit velocity</h2>
      </p>

      <p>
      Code Time integrates with Git, so you can see your speed, frequency, and top files across your commits.
      </p>

      <p>
      <img src="https://swdc-vscode.s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/commit-velocity.png"/>
      </p>

      <p>
      <h2>It’s safe, secure, and free</h2>
      </p>

      <p>
      We never access your code: We do not process, send, or store your proprietary code. We only provide metrics about programming, and we make it easy to see the data we collect.
      </p>

      <p>
      Your data is private: We will never share your individually identifiable data with your boss. In the future, we will roll up data into groups and teams but we will keep your data anonymized.
      </p>

      <p>
      Free for you, forever: We provide 90 days of data history for free, forever. In the future, we will provide premium plans for advanced features and historical data access.
      </p>

      <p>
      Code Time also collects basic usage metrics to help us make informed decisions about our roadmap.
      </p>

      <p>
      <h2>Get in touch</h2>
      </p>

      <p>
      Enjoying Code Time? Let us know how it’s going by tweeting or following us at <a href="https://twitter.com/software_hq">@software_hq</a>.
      </p>

      <p>
      We recently released a new beta plugin, Music Time for VS Code, which helps you find your most productive songs for coding. You can learn more <a href="https://www.software.com">here</a>.
      </p>

      <p>
      Have any questions? Please email us at <a href="mailto:support@software.com">support@software.com</a> and we’ll get back to you as soon as we can.
      </p>

      <p></p>

      </body>
      </html>
      ]]>
    </description>

  <!-- please see http://www.jetbrains.org/intellij/sdk/docs/basics/getting_started/build_number_ranges.html for description -->
  <idea-version since-build="164"/>

  <!-- please see http://www.jetbrains.org/intellij/sdk/docs/basics/getting_started/plugin_compatibility.html
       on how to target different products -->
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>

  <application-components>
    <!-- Add your application components here -->
    <component>
      <implementation-class>com.softwareco.intellij.plugin.SoftwareCo</implementation-class>
    </component>
  </application-components>

  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <postStartupActivity implementation="com.softwareco.intellij.plugin.PluginPostStartupActivity"/>
    <toolWindow anchor="left" secondary="true" factoryClass="com.softwareco.intellij.plugin.tree.CodeTimeToolWindowFactory" icon="/com/softwareco/intellij/plugin/assets/paw-grey-rotated.png" id="Code Time"/>
  </extensions>

  <actions>
    <group class="com.softwareco.intellij.plugin.actions.CustomDefaultActionGroup" description="Code Time menu actions" id="CustomDefaultActionGroup" text="Code Time">
      <add-to-group anchor="before" group-id="MainMenu" relative-to-action="HelpMenu"/>
      <action class="com.softwareco.intellij.plugin.actions.CodeTimeMetricsAction" description="View your latest coding metrics" id="CodeTimeMetrics" text="Code time dashboard"/>
      <action class="com.softwareco.intellij.plugin.actions.SoftwareTopFortyAction" description="Top 40 most popular songs developers around the world listen to as they code" id="SoftwareTopFortyAction" text="Software top 40"/>
      <action class="com.softwareco.intellij.plugin.actions.SoftwareDashboardAction" description="View your KPM metrics" id="SoftwareDashboardAction" text="Web dashboard"/>
      <action class="com.softwareco.intellij.plugin.actions.SoftwareLoginAction" description="To see your coding data in Code Time, please log in to your account." id="SoftwareLoginAction" text="Log in to see your coding data"/>
      <action class="com.softwareco.intellij.plugin.actions.ToggleStatusBarAction" description="Toggle the Code Time status bar metrics." id="ToggleStatusBarAction" text="Show/hide status bar metrics"/>
    </group>
  </actions>

</idea-plugin>